What's up?
Guys, I have the best news of all time.
I'm not hot.
Man's not hot.
You know why?
I bought an AC.
I will never be hot again.
No more fever dreams.
I don't give a shit what the weather is like outside.
I can control my own climate.
I feel like Zeus.
This is insane.
Is this how you Americans feel all the time?
This is nuts, man.
This is the best investment I've ever made in my life.
I would have paid twice the amount I paid.
Holy shit.
I'm not in America.
I'm in Denmark.
But the summer here is killing right now.
Stepping outside is like stepping into an oven.
Although today is not that bad, actually.
Last week was bonkers, okay?
Like I was sweating so much, I think I lost a couple pounds.
Just from sweat.
It was horrible.
I'm sitting in long socks now.
Long, you know, I have jeans on.
No more, you know, shorts.
No more sitting here naked.
It's crazy.
Yeah, it's called air conditioning.
And you know what?
The machine is at 1%.
It's on, like, silent mode.
And it's still, like, sometimes a little too cold.
It's crazy.
Woo!
This is the best thing ever.
Yeah, the long johns.
Exactly.
Isn't it expensive?
It was expensive.
I paid 10,000 kroners for it.
Which is, I don't even know, 1,200, 1,300 euros or something?
It was the last one in stock of all the retailers online.
I could not find the model that I wanted anywhere else.
So they re... I had to pay a premium for it.
But you know what, guys?
This is the best investment of all time.
I would gladly go into debt to buy this thing again.
This is crazy.
Like, you can't put a price on well-being, you know?
And having a nice climate inside.
Wow!
I'm so happy.
I really am so happy.
I can sleep normally now as well.
No more fucking sweating during the night and waking up and...
Oh.
I don't have to care about my computer producing a bunch of heat anymore.
It solves all my issues.
My life has changed.
That's the price of a car, is it?
Must be a really cheap car, then.
In Denmark, you probably can't get a car for that, unless it's, like, a real shit bucket.
AC... Yeah, I know ACs are common everywhere else in the world, you know?
But, like, Germany, Denmark, Sweden, Finland, all these other...
France...
Maybe not Spain.
But, like, Belgium and...
Uh...
Dutchland, you know?
All those lands, they don't have AC because we haven't been needing it for a while, right?
But fucking global warming is here, and it's getting hotter and hotter every year.
We need to implement this in every home.
Electricity bill is not even that crazy, actually.
It's super efficient.
I think I'm paying...
I calculated this.
So, lat...
Yesterday, I paid...
Or a...
I used 1.7 kilowatt hours.
Which I think in...
The prices here is, like, 10 kroners?
12 kroners or something?
Like, 1.5 euros?
I would gladly pay that every day.
Yeah.
Super cheap to run.
My computer...
Takes up way more electricity.
Please play Control and Alan Wake games.
Fun fact, uh...
I actually debated whether or not to play Alan Wake or XCOM.
I decided on XCOM.
But I was so close to playing Alan Wake, actually.
Maybe soon.
Oh, man.
Yeah, uh...
Like, I obviously want to play Control, but...
So, the way I understand it, you've got to play Alan Wake first.
Because it's all, like, one big universe.
And it's all connected, right?
And there's also Alan Wake 2.
But you've got to play that after Control, I think.
We're playing Binding of Isaac now.
Mr. Streamer, I only want to watch wins today.
No losing, please.
Oh, you got it.
Dude, I am in top fit shape right now.
I'm not hot.
Man's not hot.
Like, I will only win.
I'm telling you, the only reason I ever lost in this game is because it was too hot outside.
There's no script today.
We don't need it.
Not with this climate.
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
Let's get to it.
Isaac!
I don't even remember what I did last.
Do we have a win streak?
Oh!
What?
I could have sworn I won last time.
Hold on, I got to clean my glasses.
I feel like I'm seeing wrong.
It says minus one.
Let me get my microfiber.
Okay, let me see.
No, that's still minus one.
Fuck.
I did actually lose them.
That's unacceptable.
We need to fix that.
What do I want to do?
Kind of want to play with Apollyon.
Also kind of want to play with Euleth.
I mean, look at these achievements we have here.
There's almost no achievements on Euleth.
There's only one on Apollyon.
Bethany doesn't have many.
Isaac has a bunch now.
Dude, how about...
How do I do this E?
How about...
Wait, where are you?
Specialized assaysal time.
I feel like we got to do it.
Oh yeah.
Oh my god!
Dude, I'm so pumped.
Okay.
I can't tell you how much...
It makes me ha...
Oh wait, I have to remember how to play this.
Oh, it's so weird.
Playing this game again?
Oh no, that was...
Guys, I'm not playing well.
I have to remember how this works.
Okay, there we go.
I've been playing so much XCOM lately.
This is so weird, seeing this.
Okay, give me this.
Do we have any destructible rocks?
Doesn't look like it.
Oh!
Oh, fuck!
Okay, guys.
This is just a warm-up, man.
I'm rusty as hell.
It's fine, though.
We have one bomb.
Oh.
Oh, oh, oh, look at this.
Oh, that's too bad.
Wait, I can actually hit him through here.
We got to get some HP going.
Maybe I'll do some speed running today, actually.
Do the boss rush thing?
Not sure if I'll do that in this run, though.
Let's play it safe here.
Oh, I see it.
X.
Marks the spot.
Massive.
That's so good for me.
Mom's bottle of pills.
Why is mom into all these pills, anyway?
That's what I want to know.
Shit!
Yeah, I don't even know how I could have avoided that.
I got completely taken out back to the shed, you know?
Here we go.
Dingalicious!
Boink!
Oh, god.
I'm playing so bad.
Wait, oh, there's flies!
I didn't even see them.
Oi!
Yeah, this is not going well, guys.
Eugh.
This is a rough start.
Maybe I shouldn't have picked the specialized Seizel to begin with.
He's kind of hard to get back into.
I should probably pick something a little more easy to play.
Just to get used to the way the game works, you know?
Well, now my buffer is gone.
Actually, that's not really a thing on this character.
But you know what I mean.
Okay, what is the plan even?
I think we want to try and either kill Isaac or we go Satan, you know?
The Satan spawn.
We'll have to see.
I need money!
I got surrounded!
That was so bad.
No money in any of these.
Okay, this is going to be a great item.
Dead Tooth.
An aura around Isaac?
Hmm.
Eh.
Not that good.
I would say that is a C-tier item.
Nah-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I could also bomb something.
There is a chest.
I'm gonna bomb it.
I should have done it here in case there was a secret.
I messed it up.
It's fine, though.
I mean, if you think about it, I only lost half a black heart.
Because I start with two black hearts, right?
So it's actually not that bad.
We're totally chilling.
Okay, I'm not gonna go in there.
Oh, no!
Oh!
Not bad.
Oh, that's so satisfying.
The emperor.
Um.
You know what?
No.
No, no, no.
Um.
No.
Not yet.
Two keys for that.
Uh, yeah.
Why not?
Ooh!
That was totally worth...
Now we can buy the whole shop.
Very good.
Oh, the aura is actually working against those flies.
Got one key.
Rainbow baby.
Oh, I don't like that one.
I can't even get it.
I gotta find a bomb first.
The way he bounced off that rock scared me for a second.
I love this song.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, oh.
Oh!
Oh, he exploded!
Oh, shit!
Oh, that's real bad.
I'm not gonna go in yet.
We have only one HP.
This may be a short run.
It is the warm-up run.
It doesn't really count.
Oh.
Nice.
Mom's coin purse.
Uh, yeah, actually.
Let's see what we get.
Oh.
Range down.
Oh!
Not worth.
That was the worst round of pills of all time.
That was very unlucky.
You can't win them all.
Oh, the charge is so slow now.
Hey, at least this guy's easy.
Oh!
Wait, how did he die so fast?
I'm confused.
Judgment.
Oh.
Yeah, I guess I'll keep this.
I could go in there, but I don't really have the hearts for it.
I'm gonna save for angels.
Oh, wait.
Wrong way.
Down.
Saving for the angels.
Dude, I feel so naughty.
I'm drinking hot coffee.
With long johns on.
When the sun is shining outside.
Ha ha!
He he he.
Woo!
Good feeling, yo.
Come here.
Yo.
I like that I pushed them away as well.
That feels especially nice.
The chain reactions you can cause, you know.
Are quite spectacular.
Oh my god.
I got hit.
That's crazy.
Oh, the way they just...
Explode into guts.
Incredible.
I'm excited.
I have not been lucky with the pills.
The pill's a bit of disaster.
Not bad.
Oh!
Oh, yeah.
What a feeling.
The cool thing about the...
You know, when you hit them with the first short attack.
You push them into other enemies.
And then you shoot them.
And it, you know...
It spreads from there.
Punching bag.
Uh...
It's okay.
It'll help me survive a bit more.
Yeah, look.
He's absorbing.
I don't have money.
So, I shouldn't go in there.
Actually, I should.
Because I have infinite keys.
Um...
Don't really want anything here.
I think it's maybe time to start donating some more money to the machine.
That was so nice.
Spread it.
Spread the disease.
Dude, this was a smooth-ass level.
I did well.
This guy's a maniac, though.
Oh, God.
Okay, you're gonna jump.
Oh, that was funny.
There we go.
Once again.
Not bad.
Oh, yee-hee!
What a dodge!
Ha-ha!
No angels.
Damn.
Man, oh, man.
I have four bombs.
Should we look for a secret?
This could be a secret right there.
Yeah, looking good.
Let me check the bottom, uh, room.
There's also something...
Oh, no.
This can't be a secret on the left.
Nope.
Definitely not.
But maybe up here.
I think this may be it.
Beautiful.
Oh, we're definitely doing this.
Come on.
There we go.
Uh...
Ooh!
Huge!
Oh, my God!
Oi!
Thank you.
Jesus.
And Liberty Cab.
I don't want that.
Yeah, okay.
I'm happy now.
That was so worth it.
I think that may have saved the run.
Not that it needed saving, but...
It's like an insurance policy on the already saved and amazing run that we have.
Pretty...
Pretty good.
Moving on.
Guys!
I hope we get to see an angel.
I wanna...
Actually, we have to see angels.
Because I want to kill them and take their keys.
This is one of the plants we have on this run.
Oi!
Shoop-da-voop!
That's a good item.
Let me actually use it.
Oh, I got hit!
Nah.
Yeah, we got shoop-da-voop.
I am gonna be using my active item religiously this time around.
Uh, wait.
How does this work?
Ah!
Actually, that's not bad!
That's really good for me.
I like...
Easier to hit the enemies with a very narrow beam, right?
Oi-oi.
Dude, my game is lagging!
I just had a lag spike.
What the hell?
Or a frame-hitch-stutter thingy.
There you are.
Wait, are there more?
Oh.
Something dropped.
Just a heart.
Ah!
That was so close.
Watch this.
Ultimate chain reaction.
Ne-ne-ne-ne-ne-o.
Ah, uh, super ball?
Boing?
You have to fire a bouncing tier.
Increases with luck.
Uh, wait.
How does that work?
There's no bouncing tier.
Maybe I just got unlucky.
I like the wiggle worm.
I keep thinking my little guy is an enemy.
Oh, I like that one.
Shitty heart, though, unfortunately.
Six coins?
Eh, why not?
We can buy another blue heart if we want to.
Or I save up for something.
You are a flies.
I think I'll take this.
Yep.
Now I'm even considering doing demons.
Nah, we're going angel, of course.
What's happening here?
Oh.
Uh, guys?
Come on.
I pushed him away.
This run turned from pretty shit to pretty good.
Real quick.
Still haven't found a treasure room.
That's unacceptable.
Let's find that first.
You also have seven bombs.
Oh no, can we not do that?
Dude, I'm having lag spikes in this room.
Is it just me, or...
I'm very sensitive to those things.
There we go.
Knockout drops.
Chance to fire fist shots.
Which have much stronger knockback.
Oh, this is the one going...
POOPOO!
I like POOPOO!
Let's go south.
That's probably just a dead end.
Wouldn't mind a bit more damage.
Oh god.
Oh, the punching bag!
Nice.
These guys are still gonna...
Yeah.
Ohoy!
My game is lagging.
It's like low frame rates.
Is there an update or something?
Oi!
What happened there?
Why did he get pushed?
I didn't touch him with the fist.
Oh, maybe I did, actually.
Yeah, maybe that's what happened.
I guess the fist is just not animated?
When you have this ca...
Oh my god, the lag.
Hold on.
What is happening?
Am I...
Do I have something running in the back or something?
Let me close down Discord.
At least minimize it.
I have no idea.
Oh!
We have a planetarium!
Okay, hold on.
I can't handle this.
Uh...
Options.
Full screen is on.
What the fuck?
What's that?
Saturnus.
Wait, didn't I have that last time?
White Halo with seven orbiting tiers.
Halo also has a chance to absorb incoming enemy shots.
Yeah.
No, wait.
This I don't remember.
I don't remember this at all.
Well, that looks funny.
Is that because of the wiggle worm?
That it's doing that.
That's weird.
We're having a party here.
Time to face the music.
Like, it is legitimately getting maybe a little too cold in my room.
Isn't that just the best ever?
No, wait.
They were still wiggling even without it.
Huh.
Okay.
But it wasn't the wiggle worm.
That's weird.
I'm gonna shoot this guy.
Right in his fistula.
Holy crap.
That went pretty good.
And we have an angel.
I don't like that pill, though.
AWOS.
Oh, AWOS.
I guess I'll do this.
He wants coins.
Hold on.
We gotta go in here right now.
Seven seals.
Grants a wandering harbinger familiar.
Spawns locusts and deals contact damage.
I don't really like that one too much, man.
Let's fight.
Wait, did I just absorb the...
Oh, that's how that works.
That's cool.
I'm using his power against himself.
Not bad.
Kinda wanna AWOS before we move on.
Let's find the decoration.
I'm gonna decorate...
so hard.
Anything in here?
There's nothing obvious.
God, it's right here there's lag spikes.
In this room.
I don't know.
What the hell is going on?
There's, like, no decorations at all.
Nothing in here.
Oh, wait.
Maybe that rock?
No, I'm not convinced.
Uh...
What?
Maybe these blue crystals on the floor?
That one.
AWOS.
Okay, I'm not sure what that is.
Scatter bombs?
Ah, well, whatever.
It'll have to suffice.
Let's get out.
No more messing about.
Like, I don't know why my game is running in such low frames.
It don't make no sense.
No tinted rocks.
What was that one again?
Less tears.
Saving my money.
Okay, we gotta get another angel to get another key piece.
This is a key part of the strategy.
Wait, what the?
What's happening with my...
Orbits now?
Huh?
Why's it doing that?
Everything got dark.
Playing it safe.
Actually, let's go do this fight club.
Jesus!
Come on, next.
Ooh, that's a lot.
I love sweeping with the laser.
Such a good feeling.
I'm gonna keep shooping.
And vooping.
Oh, man.
The gravity was strong.
What's this room?
So many chests?
Wish I could fly.
Oh, God!
Wow.
Dude, I gotta say, my Orbits are kinda good.
Like, it's really nice.
I underestimated the power of this item.
Uh-oh.
Okay.
What is that?
Yo, listen!
I actually like that one.
That one is so good.
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa!
Did he just go here?
Look, look, look, look, look!
Oh!
No.
Okay, never mind.
I thought he went to a corner.
Oh, it's going up!
It's going up!
Okay, he's not seeing anything.
Oh, here we go, here we go!
Oh, it's such a good item!
Money!
Who doesn't like money?
With money, you can purchase goods.
And it feels good.
Okay, so nothing up here.
I just wanted to check with the Yo, listen.
Navi.
But he's not going to go bzzzt when he sees, like, a tinted rock or something.
He's just going to go there and sit there, right?
Like, what is he doing?
What is he doing?
Oh, no, never mind.
Maybe he's going to go bzzzt.
Here we go!
He did the bzzzt.
Wait, there's nothing there.
Navi, are you drunk?
I'm confused.
Was Navi lying to me?
I don't know what just happened.
Okay.
Oh, God.
I hate these poopy butts.
Okay.
I'm actually going to go in here.
Sue me.
Okay, man, that's bullshit.
Did you see that scatter bomb?
Came straight at me.
Unfair.
No.
I'm actually going to blow that up.
Okay, we're running low on health here.
It ain't good.
Navi, you gotta start beeping some more.
I love it when you squeal.
Okay, we haven't gone south yet, though.
Oh, wait.
Not this way.
I could donate bombs to that guy, too.
Yeah.
I'm going to do it.
Okay.
How about, like, an item?
That would please me greatly.
Glitter bombs.
Okay.
We're going to have very weird bombs.
Hey, dude.
Come here.
We got money.
Oh, no.
Okay.
Thank God.
I didn't actually mean to buy that.
Piggybank.
Spawns coins when taking damage.
Oh!
Oh, I thought I bought it.
I thought I...
Wait.
I'm so confused.
Did I...
What's happening?
Booster pack.
Uh...
Five random cars.
I think I could take that.
Piggybank.
Hmm.
I don't want to take damage too much.
I'm going to say...
I'm not going to take any damage.
I would rather not.
Uh...
This one transformed everything into bombs.
Mom's foot.
Doub...
Doubles bombs.
Yo.
The moon?
I mean, that's not going to matter for me.
I think I'll take the Ace of Clubs.
We could turn this entire room into bombs.
It's not a bad idea.
Actually, I should have done that before and then duplicated bombs.
This one...
Ace of Clubs.
Oh, so you can also spawn enemy bombs.
And it doesn't transform the Piggybank or any of these purchasables.
Good to know.
I have learned a lot.
From this shopping session.
Oh my God.
How did I just not take damage there?
That was...
Unbelievable.
Oh, oh.
I get it.
Oh my God.
Massive battery right there?
I'm not going to take it yet.
Uh...
No.
I will blow you up, though.
Okay.
Well, I'm earning a lot of money.
I'm ready for the next shop again.
Navi is pointing out something right here.
Wait, what are you pointing out?
That's not a tinted rock, is it?
Move, I can't see.
Hold on, we gotta check.
Yeah, that doesn't look like anything to me.
Oh!
Wow!
And what is that?
That looks good.
Gemini.
Ah, okay.
It's not that great.
Better than nothing.
Uh, what is this card?
Nobody knows.
Dagas!
Oh my God.
These are really good.
Kind of want to keep, uh...
Dagas.
And then use...
The world.
Oh, but the world is not going to reveal anything to me.
I'd rather have this and remove a curse.
Yeah.
This is the way.
Ah, I'd love to get that one.
Actually, I can.
Look.
The pushing strat!
Hey!
Smart!
Bloat!
Oh God, he also did the laser.
What is happening?
I lost a lot of HP there for no reason.
Plus one health is massive.
Uh...
Still no angel!
I would like an angel.
In fact, I need the angel...
Now.
This is the last call for the angel.
I think.
No, actually, maybe it's not.
Huh.
I actually can do this.
What the hell?
No!
Okay, whatever.
I need my listen guy to listen.
Oh, listen!
There we go!
The listening is happening.
I am the best listener in the world.
Yee-hee!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
Wow!
How am I surviving?
I didn't get hit once there.
That was masterfully done.
Uh...
Empress...
Oh, yeah, right.
Oh, wait!
It's the glitter bombs that's spawning all this crap.
I get it.
We're increasing chances?
Pew-pew-pew-pew-pew-pew-pew!
Ace of Clubs.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, wait!
I didn't mean to do that, actually.
Oh, well.
I have bombs now.
Plenty bombs.
I thought Ace of Clubs was the one that doubled my bombs.
What is that?
Nod?
Leaf?
Standing still for one second will turn Isaac into stone and grant invincibility.
Ha!
No!
It removes my little guys?
Oh, never mind.
It doesn't.
Huh.
Oh.
I don't want to be standing still here.
Oh, I...
Oh, wait.
We have a curse right now.
I could remove it.
I'm gonna remove it.
Yeah, I hate that curse.
It's an annoying one.
Gemini is actually kind of...
Oh, my God.
Gemini is...
Oh, wait.
I shouldn't have taken that.
No, it's fine.
It's fine.
Yeah, I'm rich now.
Would like to get a shop.
45% angel.
How did I take damage?
The empress.
The hermit.
Oh!
That's...
Actually, I want that.
Oh, wait.
Isn't this the shop?
No, it's not the shop.
This is the shop.
Oh, look at this one.
More options.
Definitely.
Eraser.
Hmm.
Give me the pill.
I found pills.
Oh, okay.
Eraser could be interesting.
Let me see.
Throws it in the direction.
Upon striking an enemy, it will instantly destroy it and all copies of it.
Okay.
It's not erase bosses.
Can be thrown once per floor.
Yeah.
Let's just try that a bit.
I haven't ever really tried this very much.
It's time to try it.
Wait, I'm going to delete these guys.
Hey, look!
Nice!
I'm going to optimize the shit out of this.
I'm going to go back for the...
Oh, my.
Did you see the lag spike just now?
Oh, my God.
What's happening?
I've never had this issue in this game ever.
Something's wrong with my computer today.
Minus one range.
No, thanks.
Get away from me.
Okay.
Dude, this run is going well.
No complaints.
I'm going to go back up here and grab the shoop.
Blarg.
Like, I hate to make an excuse about the framerates, but I honestly think I will end up taking damage that I shouldn't have because of it.
Oh, wait.
Secret.
Can we stop with the money?
Mom!
Okay.
Mom is blue for some reason.
Is it just me, or am I kind of killing it?
That was beautiful.
Let's take the negative.
And no angel.
That's crazy.
Brother.
Give me the angels!
Wow.
Okay.
I don't actually remember whether or not I can still get angels here.
Oh, I can.
62%.
Okay.
Oh, god.
I shouldn't have done that.
I gotta start getting more HP.
The lag is crazy.
I'm gonna have to restart the game soon.
Joker.
Oh.
Hey!
Wait, wait, wait.
Guaranteed angel?
No!
I don't even see what I get.
Oh, my god.
This one is worth three.
It's probably really good, right?
Guys, we're doing it.
Spirit of the night.
Everything's all right.
Guys, I feel like we may have made a mistake.
I'm taking this.
Guppies.
Okay.
What is that even?
Oh, that's flying, isn't it?
We just got flying?
Wait.
Why did we get flying?
Oh, it's this one.
That's the one.
That's good, then.
But now we have a bit of a situation.
We don't have any HP.
That's, that's, uh...
That's not good.
Also, I forgot to bring the eraser.
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
I'm flying.
It's fine.
Oh?
Consolation prize.
Some attack speed.
I like it.
Man, so many bombs, so many coins.
Wow.
Is it just me, or are they kind of tanky right now?
Oi!
Nice.
That's mega huge.
Doubles the keys.
Why not?
40.
About to charge me.
Oi!
Scary.
HP up.
Yo!
We're so back!
Whoa!
See that worm?
That's the largest worm I've ever seen.
Oh, fuck this room.
No.
No thanks.
I'm actually just gonna say no to that.
Oh, but wait, wait.
We just had a...
No, why you gotta biz-biz me here?
Oh, wait, it's right there.
Ah!
Fuck!
Yeah, we lost all the fucking HP we had.
Great.
Stupid room.
Shit room.
Ruined the whole run, actually.
Thank you, Navi.
It's all your fault.
I hit nothing there.
That was incredible.
Get away from me.
Come on, hit him!
Okay, we got him.
Wait, did I just...
I just picked up a necklace?
Familius orbit around Isaac.
But don't they already do that?
Walnut.
Uh...
Nah.
Nope.
No thanks.
I reject.
The world is actually nice.
Let's see.
Let's just beeline it for the boss.
I feel...
kinda good about that.
Oh no.
I need HP.
Don't eye me!
Oh!
Oh, nice!
We needed that.
We needed that too!
Oh, you want keys?
I got keys for ya!
Show me what's good.
I could also donate some hearts, but I don't really need money, so...
I wanna find an arcade.
Oh, man!
Didn't even think that could happen from one of these chests that spawned from this guy, but...
You live, you learn.
He's eating a lot of my keys.
Come on.
Hello?
Oh!
Oh, wait, what?
Minus tears in this one?
I'm excited.
I don't like those pills!
Give me some good stuff.
Dude, where's my money equals power?
I feel like I had a whole...
arc where I got it almost every run, and I haven't seen it in years now.
Wire code hang...
Oh!
Not bad!
Faster charge?
That's huge, actually.
I'm not gonna give him all my keys.
Latch key.
Ooh.
Yo, this guy's actually giving some good items.
How about a blue heart?
Or a black heart?
I'll take either.
Man, he's just spawning chests left and right here.
There we go, blue heart!
Shiny rock.
Titted rocks.
Uh...
No, I don't need that.
We have...
Yo, listen.
Okay, maybe we should stop giving him keys now.
Yeah!
Ah!
Yes!
Okay, one more key.
One more key.
Watch it.
This is gonna be a great item.
Okay, well.
It's fine.
Uh, yep.
No.
Okay, that was...
That was very nice.
Very nice.
Let's do it.
Low key!
Okay, I obviously gotta get in close and do that.
Oh god.
What is happening?
Uh, we got demons.
Speed up.
Dude, where's my angels at?
I guess I shouldn't have taken the demon then.
The angel dream is dead?
All of a sudden.
I'll take this one.
Brimstone bombs.
Eww, I don't like that.
Let me just confirm it is what I think it is.
Okay, that is legitimately frickin' scary.
I gotta be careful using this.
It's a good room clear.
Arcade.
Yeah, I'm rich!
This is the place for me.
Uh...
Oh, this guy wants bombs?
Yo!
I got it!
Black hearts!
We're so back.
This is insanity.
Wait, what?
No, he blew up!
Oh, man.
What a bummer.
What a bummer, man.
Get it, bummer, man?
Oh...
Can we, like, feed him faster?
Just eat my bombs.
Eat him, eat him, eat him, eat him.
You ordered it!
You gotta eat it!
Come on.
I'm too rich.
99 coins.
Ah!
Oh!
That's a great item!
Hold on, hold on.
This is...
We can only do this once.
Only once.
We're gonna save this bad boy until the very end.
Oh, we got a secret over here.
Oy, oy, oy.
Money, money, money.
I don't need it, actually.
Why did I just pick that up?
Oh!
I'm an idiot.
I keep forgetting that happens.
Uh, I'm excited.
Battery.
Blow this up.
Fucking get out of there.
Oh!
Wait, what?
How did I not take damage just now?
Wait, I...
I took damage, and then I didn't take damage.
What?
I ran into the rock.
That was on me.
My bad.
That was a self-inflicted pain right there.
It is what it is.
Navi!
I hate when they jump.
See, I don't know what just happened there.
How did I take damage?
Wake up, wake up.
I need more blue hearts.
Range down?
No thanks.
How about range up?
Okay, well...
Apparently I can't take damage from that.
I don't know why.
Oh, oh, oh.
Definitely, definitely.
We're gonna stay here 10 years.
Please spawn a mobile gambling station.
Come on, blue hearts.
Black hearts.
Yellow hearts.
I mean, we're just getting all the money back here.
Ah, a pill.
I'm so excited every time I see a pill.
You also have seven luck.
So we really need to go get items that, you know, have a percent chance to fire something.
I swear, this game is a comedy.
It truly is.
Rich get richer.
Like, the theory is proven.
It's so dumb.
Get up here.
Oh my god.
How come I didn't take damage from that?
That was his laser.
Wait, am I immune to lasers all of a sudden?
Why?
Oh, wait.
I guess it's my brimstone beam, but I didn't bomb him just now, so how does that work?
I don't get that.
No, hell no.
I don't like that room.
Health situation is acceptable.
It's not great.
No, open your mouth.
Brother man, come on.
Wasting my time here.
Mr. Poom spawns a large bomb?
I don't think so.
I'll keep the strength.
I don't know how I just took damage.
What happened?
There's some things in this game that I just don't understand at all.
Confusing.
Okay, it's, it's, it's, uh, boss time.
It lifts.
Not for long, I can tell you that.
Oh my god.
I don't know if I'm doing this right.
This is, this is not good.
Jesus Christ.
Where are the angels?
I guess they're gone forever.
Curved horn.
Wow.
Two damage?
Yo, that's actually kind of massive.
Okay, guys.
I can't take any of this.
Or I will die.
Uh, oh man.
Yeah, I don't need this.
It is unfortunate.
Fuck it.
Health situation is still terrible.
Die!
What?
Change directions.
Okay, man.
It's over.
Good run.
It was a good warm-up run.
I'm gonna see how we can win this one.
Like, it has never been more over.
And my damage is utterly...
Disastrous.
And I have fucking lag spikes like crazy.
Like, frame...
Pacing issues.
Or frame time issues.
Something is utterly wrong right now.
No thanks.
Yeah, I shouldn't go in there.
Bad idea.
Strength?
That actually gives me one health.
But it's not gonna matter because I don't have a red heart.
I'm using this thing now.
I gotta do it to survive.
Oh, well.
I don't know...
How anyone's gonna survive this.
What?
Oh, there's a guy up there.
Wait.
Are they changing positions around the room?
I don't understand how that just happened.
There were suddenly people in the bottom.
Like, these inanimate objects suddenly became animated.
I'm not sure what just happened.
I'm gonna take a quick break.
I gotta take a piss.
Right back.
Okay, here we are.
First...
First run didn't count.
It was, of course, a warm-up run.
Let's try and go fast now.
Speed mode engaged.
We also have a curse, which sucks.
It is what it is.
Dark bomb.
He wants to take your...
Oh, wait.
What is this guy doing again?
Consumes...
Oh, that's good for me!
Oh, yeah.
Not bad.
Oh, my God.
Really?
Yeah.
Come on.
Pick him up.
Anything good?
No?
Okay.
Ah!
Oh!
Wow!
This guy's gonna pay off like crazy.
Oh, I forgot to restart the game.
My fucking framerate.
Guys, can I restart the game and have it saved?
I'm asking you.
Rotund.
So, if I just click exit now, it should be okay, right?
Okay.
Hold on.
Click here.
Let me try and...
Oh, yeah.
I see that.
And...
Let me see if anything's running on my computer that shouldn't run.
No?
Everything looks the way it should look.
I have no idea.
We launch.
There we go.
Maybe it'll work.
We'll see.
Continue.
I don't think I've ever clicked that button in my life.
This is the first time I'm clicking the continue button.
Isn't that weird?
Wow.
What's that one?
Mom's eye?
Chance to fire additional...
Tear...
Uh, yeah.
Okay, I still have framerate issues.
I don't know what the fuck is going on today.
This is some bullshit.
I don't know.
Like, it feels...
Oh my god!
Did you see that lag?
Hold on.
I can't.
Uh, we gotta clear this room.
I'm gonna have to try something.
I can't play like this.
Like, I have input lag now as well.
Like, when I fucking move my character, there's like a slight millisecond delay now.
I'm gonna have to restart again.
Uh,
here.
I don't know what to do.
Uh, let me try something.
What can I try?
Maybe it's like a setting.
Okay.
I tried to remove the bordered fullscreen now.
Maybe that's what did it.
Even though it's been on all this time.
Who knows?
Let's see.
I mean, it's still there.
It feels like the game is playing in...
50 frames per second.
Which is insane.
Because it feels like...
Well, 120, usually.
I don't know.
I'll just have to live with it.
At least I'll have an excuse.
For when things go wrong.
Maybe a restart would do it.
On the computer, I mean.
I've never had this issue.
It's crazy.
I guess it doesn't matter for me.
Oh man, I need bombs!
There's stuff everywhere!
Hold on.
We got a blue heart and a...
A secret thingy.
Oh god, I can't do it, can I?
We don't have bombs.
Move on.
We're speedrunning.
Ain't nobody got time for that.
Huge.
Extra HP on Azazel is always...
Mwah!
Ares.
I'm moving fast enough.
That's the one that builds up.
Yo!
Wow!
That's huge!
This is...
This is the run?
Rarely do you get a start as good as this one.
Good.
Rolls are rich now.
We can actually go back.
Hold on.
I gotta get one more coin.
Let's get to the shop.
Oh, I have a bomb.
I could get the coin there, but...
Champion.
I think I want that.
More damage.
And then up here.
I didn't mean to open that.
It was an instinct.
Pure instinct.
Pentagram!
Yay!
That's a good one.
We're going angels.
Oh, I don't have a key.
Shit.
No!
I'm playing like...
Dark shit right now!
I need to pull myself together.
Oh, wait.
Is this...
Oh, okay.
Homing effect.
I like that.
This room is so sad.
It breaks my heart.
Can I not...
Rosary beat.
Increase the chance of...
When a devil room...
Angels!
That's very nice.
Nice.
I think I'm in good speed here.
I'm doing great.
Bad trip.
Deals one heart of damage.
Turns into a full health pill.
Wait, what?
This one's not going to do anything to me, I guess.
Right?
Like, it's just...
Yeah.
Weird.
Choop!
Oh, that was so good.
No angel!
Damn!
We did so well, though.
Speed!
Go!
Okay.
The name of the game is to get a bunch of keys from angels.
Oh, those guys...
I thought I was out of range.
That was surprising.
My reflection.
Oh, hold on a minute.
This one is...
The one that shoots backwards.
Uh...
I don't hate it.
Honestly.
Like, it's okay.
The chariot...
No.
Uh...
Yeah.
Oh, God.
Niii!
Piss off!
That was so badly played.
Oh, no.
I'm gonna blow it up.
This way?
I'm not really excited about any of this.
Random stat...
Down?
Only down?
Yikes.
Naaah!
Holy crap!
Let's do it.
The frail?
I've never seen this.
Or have I?
No, I've seen it.
Dark food.
Man.
What do you mean?
No angel?
What does a man need to do to get angel?
My mind is blown right now.
The hell?
100% chance of angel, though.
Like, this one.
Surely this is it, right?
Oh, my God.
Open it up!
Thank you.
Fucking hell.
Took forever.
Nope, nope, nope.
I'm actually gonna do this.
Hey!
Make me black hearts, go!
Poop him, poop him, poop him!
You're not gonna poop?
Wait, why does he do it on the next room?
Is that just how he operates?
That's like his MO?
Okay, we don't have time for this.
We gotta keep moving.
Eat him!
There we go.
Yo!
Okay, we're back.
One key left.
Dang.
Oh, no.
Hagalos!
I'll keep this one instead.
No, actually.
Keep this.
I could destroy this room and get the keys, but I'm not gonna.
I'm gonna.
I'm not gonna.
I thought I was gonna, but then I didn't gonna.
I'm gonna.
I realized I was low on keys.
I was too close.
That's just sad.
Okay.
You wanna eat that heart?
Eat it, eat it, eat it.
He's not gonna poop for me.
I wish he would poop for me.
Continuum!
More range?
Tears pass through walls and obstacles?
Tears that travel off the edge of the screen.
Hey!
That sounds pretty good.
Dude, that means...
That means my attacks are, like...
Infinite in both directions.
It doesn't matter which direction I shoot.
That's insane.
I got a doctor's remote.
Oh, actually, it doesn't matter.
That's not what it means.
I misunderstood the description.
I get it now.
Mostly, it's gonna be infinite.
The gate!
And we have...
100% demon!
Stai.
Thank you.
Here we go.
Uh, wait.
These fires scare me.
Uh, plus one eternal heart.
Yes!
Ah, he just ran into it.
Dummy.
A credit card!
I can't believe I just keep getting hit by these fucking flames.
What does the credit card do?
Makes everything free.
That's kind of nuts.
Are we still speedrunning?
Hold on, what's the timer?
Kinda!
No, yeah, we are!
We are, we're ahead.
But I still gotta hurry a little bit, I think.
I should have done that before I transitioned level.
I just realized.
I did it wrong.
Do I look like I care about range?
Bro, I don't...
Piss off!
Stupid little black ball.
We don't have time to gamble.
Yeah, eat him!
That's what I'm talking about!
Oh, another one!
Wow!
Black hearts galore!
I hate when they jump!
Wow!
I actually can't believe that dropped the black heart.
Okay, I...
Oh, actually...
Yeah, give me that.
I have no keys?!
What the?!
How is that even possible?!
That blows my mind.
There's an action on this one!
I saw it!
Oh ho ho ho!
They call me eagle eye!
Jesus.
Duty.
Doodette.
We gotta hurry.
We don't have time for this.
Gimpy.
I'm rich.
Yep.
I'm buying it all.
Wait, I probably should have used credit card, huh?
Credit card.
Too bad.
Too late for that now.
What does Bat Trip do?
Deals one full heart of damage.
Yeah, that one does nothing for me.
Blow it all up.
Okay, we gotta go, man.
What?
Ah!
I hate my... This game is making me hate myself.
Equality?
I didn't mean to take that.
I didn't mean to do that.
Blow it up.
Oh, I have no more bombs.
Time for Mom.
I'm getting pretty good at dealing with Mom, though.
There we go!
Yeah, here we go, baby!
Virgo... Hold on.
Can't be taking damage to activate a shield.
Oh, wait!
So this one overrides false PhD?
And we have Dead Tooth.
Nope.
Conehead.
Soul Heart.
Trying a chance to negate damage.
Take it.
Whoa.
That's pretty good.
I'm taking that.
Hey, does this guy drop a key then?
He's an angel.
Oh, no.
I got hit twice there.
I really got to focus.
Not being able to see my HP is going to be problematic here.
Even though you could say, does it really matter?
Because you don't want to get hit anyway.
It does matter.
It's psychological.
Not being able to see my HP is going to mess with me.
Hit when they poop.
Come on.
Eat the heart.
Item.
What does that do?
Double bombs.
I don't have any.
Give me one.
Or two.
No.
Not nice.
Eat the heart.
You paid for it.
Eat it.
You ordered it.
You gotta eat it.
I can't see.
Nice.
Black heart.
Blue heart.
Nice.
I didn't mean to do that.
That was a misclick.
Misclick.
Bomb for you.
Yeah.
The hell is this deal?
Why can't I apply the thing?
There we go.
Come on.
Let me put the thing on you.
There we go.
Nice.
Huge.
That was clean.
I see where you are.
Wow.
Another heart for me.
Another one.
I love when they explode next to each other.
It brings me happiness.
What's that cart?
Do it.
Make me strong.
Hoi.
Ah!
It's so weird when I'm so big.
Destroy the tomatoes.
Ansys.
Nice.
I pushed him away.
Wait.
Am I full HP?
I couldn't pick that up just now.
Uh-oh.
No.
We got a Steven out of that?
Bro.
That is the most underwhelming reward of all time.
I can't believe that.
Ace of Clops.
I like that.
Give me that one.
Yeah.
Move on.
Let's go!
Okay.
That was nice.
I mean, technically, we got two items out of it, right?
It was Steven and the item we got at the start there.
Destroy them!
Oh, I'm panicking.
I...
No.
Ansys.
Give me answers.
There's more?
What happened to that pill?
Bro, I couldn't move the gravity.
What's this?
Watch battery.
Increased hands with a little battery spawning.
Uh, no.
Not really feeling that.
I have no bombs, man.
Can't even get to the secret room.
Where's the boss?
It's down there.
I got a bomb.
Another one.
God.
This gravity!
Oh.
It's strong.
Blastocyst.
Dude, there's so many of them.
I'm just getting HP on HP on HP.
It's insane.
Okay.
We need to stop collecting HP.
No!
My corner can suck my ass!
What the fuck?
Jesus.
It's over!
I don't know how the fuck I'm taking all this damage.
It's straight up over.
This is absolute insanity.
Yeah.
I don't mean...
I don't know.
I don't even know what I can do.
This is insane.
Like, I don't even know what the fuck happened in the last one minute.
That is...
making my blood boil.
Holy shit!
That just pissed me off.
Let's go Eden.
Holy crap.
Gain invincibility and bonus speed.
I can't even...
I don't even want to think about what just happened.
I'm...
We can fly.
That's something.
Ah, okay.
I'll...
do this as well.
We have a buffer.
It is so weird not having a laser.
Oh, he's just gonna keep spawning them.
Oh, that's annoying.
Actually, you know what?
You want to destroy this for me?
Come here.
Please just throw a bomb.
It's like he knows.
I don't understand.
Come over here and bomb the rock!
There we go.
Not even worth it.
Fuck.
Hell.
Holy shit.
Oh, I forgot I had this.
That's actually pretty good.
I should have used that.
Botfly!
I dig that.
Release the poops.
Wow.
Okay, we have some money now.
Okay.
I'm totally gonna horn this guy.
That was pretty good.
Good damage.
Come on.
Please be good pills this time.
Alright.
Not bad.
I like it.
Move on.
Solid.
God.
Why do I always get this sense that I really want to eat cake when I play this game?
I'm having the craziest cravings.
Like a birthday cake or something, you know?
I could totally just devour that right now.
Like a cake with layers.
This room is going to be crazy.
Oh!
How am I not getting hit?
Never mind.
And we lost all demon.
I shouldn't have said anything.
I jinxed it.
We got a PhD over there.
I am intrigued in that.
Buy that.
With that.
I shall purchase it when I have money.
Oh wait!
I can fly!
I keep forgetting.
I can actually just go into the stones here if I want to.
Get with some healing.
Got the boss here.
Man.
We are going to try and get angels again.
Although it has been a while since we have had a nice brimstone.
You know?
Like on a character not a Seizel.
Oh!
I don't have a key.
Don't do this to me.
I better find a key.
How is this room real?
Wow!
There is a lot.
We are not done yet.
Wait.
How do you just take extra damage there at the end?
Must have done something.
Wasn't there a heart somewhere that I...
Oh yeah.
In here.
Give me that.
Um.
You know what?
I'm going to go in here.
We're only going to take a little bit of damage, right?
So it may actually be worth...
Okay!
I guess it was worth.
And now we can get the treasure up here.
It's looking up.
Ugh.
Terrible item.
Man.
Okay.
Fine.
I'll take it.
Let me also destroy this guy.
10% demon chance there.
Oh my god.
It's a disco.
Magician is super good.
But I need some more damage.
Like, I'm at 2.9 damage.
That's just not good.
No.
Wait.
I can just leave.
No.
I can't.
Okay.
Rackman.
What a name.
This is a weird enemy.
One of the worst items.
Maybe I'm going to start going into...
The really difficult areas.
But I can't even handle the normal areas.
You know?
How am I going to survive in there?
I see a secret here.
Okay.
Dude.
This blue map is actually wilding.
I don't like this room.
Surprised I did that without taking damage.
Okay.
Fuck this.
Yo.
Two soul hearts.
Ooh.
That's actually straight into...
The demon...
Bank.
And I think I want to do demons.
Always wanted to do a demon.
I have 22 coins.
Never mind.
I have more than that now.
Very nice.
Oh
my god.
Flying is wild.
Isaac farts and poops every 30 seconds?
Nah.
Broken watch!
Nice!
And that one...
Experimental pill.
Tears up speed.
I like that, I think.
Yeah, that's good.
I'm happy.
I'm taking every advantage I can get.
The only problem we have in this run is that we need some more damage.
If we can get that sorted, I think we're actually cooking.
And this time with diesel.
Nah, why you gotta do that to me?
Very unlucky!
I'm unlucky!
That's a weird room.
Destroy this snake!
I'm not keeping track of the numbers here.
For the watch.
Sweet.
Actually, secret, secret.
What a weird room.
I mean, that's the setup for some stepping right there.
But it's not happening, because I want to have buffers.
So in general, like, step rooms are just not that great.
Because you don't want to get rid of your buffers, right?
It's only good if you have red hearts.
And only red hearts.
Free lemonade.
No.
Don't want that.
Although it is, I guess, damage.
Not worth.
Oh, do I want magician or strength?
I think this one.
I'm actually gonna use it now.
I don't have much damage, so this can help me with that.
At least a little bit.
By hitting more shots.
What?
I didn't even hit him!
Dude, he's tanky.
Here he comes.
Do I take a demon?
What if we wait for the angels?
Let's have a look.
What the?
Why am I shooting so fast?
Oh, the broken watch!
I see.
Ocular Rift is actually huge.
Oh!
That would make us two out of three on conjoined.
But I feel like this is what I need to do some damage.
Because I'm lacking damage.
I'm taking that.
Maybe I'll take this too.
No.
Only one.
Let's not get greedy.
What's up, guys?
It is very satisfying to use that.
This is good.
I'm gonna die here.
No, I'm not.
I saw my death flash before my eyes, though.
That's why I said that.
Okay, so we actually need luck.
I like that.
Get sucked into the black hole.
Oh, wait.
I feel like that's a bug.
The black hole doesn't obey the...
the slowed down time.
Like, the duration of it is still full-time.
Or real-time.
That's gotta be like a bug, right?
Man, you're tangy.
Two secrets.
Love that I can just see them.
That's thanks to the tail that we just got a black heart, I think.
Come here.
Okay, what do we get?
Black hole!
Black holes on black holes.
I...
I think I like it.
Let's go full black hole.
36% demon.
That's not a loss.
Witch.
Ho-hoi!
Oh, it doesn't deal damage to them, or what?
It just sucks them in, that's it.
Boomerang is actually pretty good, but...
I don't want this.
I do like these pills.
Yeah, I'm happy with that.
Very nice.
Uh, so we have treasure room, we have that.
We can...
We got both secrets.
Let's go.
I feel good.
It's even slowed down.
Couldn't be better.
Oh, the black hole is helping with damage.
Any more luck?
Come on, demon!
Yes!
Money equals power, or the book of sin.
Uh...
We need damage?
I would say money equals power, and then we just save up.
It's not terrible.
Let's find a dollar bill that gives a hundred coins.
That was a scary room.
Ah, nice!
Mom's ring.
For some reason, every time I pick that up...
Oh, we got AWOS!
It feels like an item in World of Warcraft, you know?
Like, it's a nice loot.
God, I love Broken Watch.
I wonder, though, if time also moves slower, like, in the timer up there.
I doubt it.
Wait, let me see.
Actually, I can't test that here.
Next time it slows down, I'm gonna see.
Oh!
That's definitely an AWOS spot.
AWOS!
No!
I don't even want it.
It's a straw.
Ew.
Atrocious.
Maybe there's a reward here?
No reward.
Let's go to secrets!
Why didn't they react?
Oh my gosh.
The parasite.
That is...
Actually okay.
That's a decent item.
Let me see if time moves slower.
It doesn't.
Broken Watch does not affect time.
It's kind of funny.
Do I have, like, Curse of Darkness or something?
Everything feels so dark.
Wait, how do I get to that other secret room?
Why are you here, maybe?
I can't really spend my money.
I need it for money equals power.
But...
Mom's Purse...
Mom's Purse is so good.
And it gets us to 3 out of 3 on Yes Mother.
Although that does nothing, so...
What did I get?
Increases duration of status effects.
Which one?
Oh, like, Broken Watch, maybe?
More duration on time slow.
The sun is wild.
Oh god.
Get away from me.
Man, this room sucks.
Temperance.
I could...
Do that.
I have the sun, right?
Yeah, I'm happy with that.
What the heck?
Whoa-ho-ho-ho-ho!
What the?
I guess we're donating.
This is gonna be fun.
This is the most self-harm I've ever done.
Holy shit!
Money troubles are gone.
And we get a lot of money for money equals power.
That was incredible.
Ah!
And we're slowed down.
Like, this is going perfect.
Wait, it doesn't feel like it's slowed down.
What?
This doesn't feel slow at all.
The fuck is...
Oh my god, I'm dying!
Why is he so wild?
Fucking calm down!
Duh!
Binky!
This was so bad.
Do I even want anything in here?
Maybe the left one.
The mark...
Oh, that's actually good.
Goat hit.
Oh, that's also good!
I want...
Both.
No!
No.
Yes!
I shouldn't have done it!
I should...
Bad boy!
Ah!
Why am I like this?
Kill...
Oh, now we're slowed down.
Uh-huh.
I don't like...
I don't like this corridor!
It's displeasing me.
Actually, it's fine.
Let's go south and get that secret room.
Wait, never mind?
Maybe over here?
Man, getting all that money really helped me with my damage.
This room would have been so hard to do without flying.
High chance I would have just died in here.
Guys, can we turn all our money into a hundred money in the arcade?
What is this guy giving me?
He's battery, right?
Not too bad.
In fact, all of those hearts are big right now.
Oh my god.
Am I gonna spend my money?
Dye shorts?
Little...
Little baggy can hold two pills.
This is...
This is like going full pill.
I like it.
Explosive dial fear.
No!
Wait, what did we get?
Experimental pill.
Oh, in terms of speed?
Okay.
That didn't feel good, did it?
Alright.
Dude, why am I shooting so many black holes all of a sudden?
Get away from me!
That's for you!
Get into my hole.
Why are they...
Are they too fat?
What?
Like, what?
I think they were too fat.
They didn't fit in the hole.
Oh, I think we gained a heart from that pill!
That's what we got.
Hey, library!
Just one book.
That's the saddest library of all time.
I don't even like this book.
But I will use it in here.
Just in case it blew up like a secret...
Wait, there is a secret.
Ha ha ha!
Wow.
I'm glad that that was used there.
And I didn't, uh...
Got speed up on some other room, you know?
That could have killed me.
Masterfully done.
Mystery egg.
I don't like the description for that one.
That's disturbing.
Minus one range.
Hey, that's good!
So was that.
Spider baby.
Nah.
Very underwhelming.
Crab item.
No, wait.
Go left and then down.
Are we ready?
I'm gonna black hole you, mom.
That's for you.
Route control.
Oh, wait a minute.
I don't even...
Wait, have we actually, uh...
Gone home on this character?
Because we have an opportunity to do it, right?
We have telepills.
Oh, shit.
I...
No, mom!
Stop!
I'm taking, uh...
That one.
Okay, we got...
We got demons.
Oh, no.
I don't like what I'm seeing.
Like, where's my brimstone at?
Shit.
What do I want?
I mean, Goppy's color is...
Oh, wait.
Why did I lose a heart?
I thought it was like...
If I step on these, then I take damage.
But I didn't step on them.
So, I don't know.
I'm pretty sure we already...
Did go home on this character.
Yeah.
We keep going down, baby.
Man, blue map is...
Is kind of broken.
I've been sleeping on that map.
Oh, yes.
Give me money.
It equals power.
Huh?
Oh.
Holy money!
Oh, that's a friend.
8.91 damage is pretty good.
Also, I think my lag is gone.
I haven't noticed it in a while.
No more frame drops.
It's been clean.
Oh, yes.
Woo!
Woo-hoo-hoo!
That's massive.
I like this one.
One more luck?
That's huge for me.
Speed...
Whatever.
It's good.
Heal me up.
I don't want that.
This means more black holes.
Nope.
Actually, yes.
Push it.
Ha-ha-ha!
Not bad, eh?
Somehow, I'm staying afloat with the hearts here.
I don't know how I'm doing it.
Okay, I shouldn't have said anything.
I'm sinking again.
Oh, he's a friend.
More pills!
I didn't mean to eat the other pill.
I forgot I had two pills equipped.
Black card!
Yes!
No, I don't want that.
Damn.
I've got a rotating boy as well.
Ha-ha!
Rotating adult.
Don't you just love it when adults rotate?
It's one of my favorites.
I honestly couldn't even see the bombs.
There was so much crap on my screen, I had no idea.
Fish in a barrel.
I just want a character that has some sort of innate ability to just replace all cards and all items, everything in the game, with pills.
That would give me happiness.
Like, full pill style.
It's like opening a present, you know, when I eat one.
Yeah, sometimes you get cold, but...
Man, it feels good when you don't.
Plus one to lower stat, so that's speed?
Okay.
Guys, we gamble.
Dark Prince's...
Wait, loss is power?
While at one red heart, the crown activates and gives two fire rate, range, and shot speed.
So it's not active now.
I actually need to get a red heart.
That's what you're saying.
Yeah.
Or...
What?
I'm not sure.
Okay.
We move on.
Actually, hold on.
Treasure room.
I haven't even found that.
I can't move on without that.
Also, this black hole, my active, it's actually a shit item.
Okay.
It's pretty good.
I'll take it back.
That was beautiful.
Wonderful.
Like, I...
So, yes, mother, you get a little knife that is like behind you and it...
it does nothing.
At least, not in my experience.
It is the most useless upgrade of all time.
Now, conjoined, on the other hand.
See, now we're talking, right?
That's what an upgrade is.
62 coins.
Can we get to 100?
100.
Huge with a black heart.
Come on, treasure room me.
Wait.
Why is there no treasure room?
What?
This map doesn't have a treasure room?
That's weird.
Like, I've never seen that.
That is just some weird stuff.
It's not even like we're playing a challenge.
Oh, fuck.
I used all my bombs.
I thought I had like 50 bombs.
Whoops.
I guess we're leaving.
Are we?
Yes, we are.
No, we're not!
See ya!
I love you.
Yeah.
Pretty good.
Okay, now we go out.
Now we're done.
Or do we?
Yes.
I can't even take that.
Because I'll die.
I would love to take it.
But I can't.
Cold coffee is actually not that bad.
Time to get some secrets going.
Actually, yeah, I have bombs now again.
He hit like a thousand meters shot with that rifle there.
And I just walked into it.
We can't let stuff like that happen.
Oh, no!
Evil.
Well, now we have all the money in the world.
This is all the damage.
I'm even getting some luck going here.
Uh.
No.
No thanks.
Secret on the right.
Let's go get it.
Wait, huh?
I guess I come to that from the bottom?
Confusing.
Oh, no.
Is it over?
I don't want it to be over!
Fuck!
This run is awesome!
Okay, thanks.
We're back.
The run is not over.
Jimboy.
Jimbo.
Jimmylicious.
Get slowed, nerd.
What do you want?
I hate when they whistle.
Okay, that's a friend.
It's over.
We're so dead.
Come on, secret room.
Save me.
Um.
Yeah.
Range.
Okay.
What about a health up?
Oh, no.
Not this!
I'm dead.
It lashed out at me.
Fucking hell.
Fucking fuck.
I think we go for it.
It lives.
Eat the hearth of Black Hole.
Holy crap.
Okay, okay.
Here we go.
Focus.
What the hell is that?
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Oh!
Copy!
Ooh.
We're not gonna win!
I don't know how to win this game!
Wait, Samson has like...
No achievements at all!
Like zero!
Have we even tried this character?
Samson.
You have nothing.
You have eyebrows.
Uh, your damage is decent.
I mean, cup...
I can't stand it.
Wait, I'm blinking!
Is that a Samson thing?
My eyebrows.
This could be a stepper.
We got three red hearts.
If we find a bunch of red hearts...
Another PhD.
No, that's a coupon.
Never mind.
It looks like a PhD.
Imagine I find...
14 coins to...
What the...
Oh, right!
Wait, we have played this character before.
So wait, how does that...
How does that work?
When does it...
I don't understand when it activates.
Or what needs to happen.
But what I do need...
Uh, know is that you gotta go fast when it's active.
So you can get maximum usage.
Fuck.
My range is atrocious.
Chop him up!
Chopity chop!
Go into IHOP.
Pancakes.
Ah, we're too slow.
Let me start chopping.
Did we get a treasure room yet?
No, we didn't.
I gotta find one first.
South.
Oh man, what a detour.
No bombs.
Stop crying.
No problem.
We're going full demon.
And that's a promise.
Dude, the Joker card is probably one of the best cards in the game.
I just realized how good it is.
Because a lot of the time in this game...
All you want is to get to a demon or an angel room, right?
That just allows you to go.
Immediately.
No matter what.
Turdlings?
I think I'm going to die in here.
Chua!
Mom!
Holy!
Why is this boss so difficult?
Yeah, here we go.
Slice the turds!
Slice them!
Health.
I think it just activates after a certain amount of time in a room.
And maybe that gets amplified by the kills you get.
But there is, like, a timer on that.
We got a secret rock.
But no bombs.
Oh!
I don't know how I'm doing it.
Like, I'm kind of doing it right now.
Very nice.
But no keys now.
Wait, we have a 100% demon right now.
Here we go!
Slice and dice!
It runs out too fast.
Let's go.
Give me any...
I'm going to cheese-configurate the small one.
Never mind.
That was good.
Another black heart.
Full demon.
Where is my brimstone?
Hold on.
If I take this, I can take the other one too.
But I forget what the other one is.
Can I get past this without...
I can't.
Okay, I have the occult.
No, not that one!
But it's going to give me two out of three on Levi...
No, no, I don't want it.
It sucks.
Ass.
I can't stand that one.
I refuse flat out.
Deal rejected.
I'm so angry!
But I'm losing HP to these noobs in here.
Oh yeah, it's going up killing spree.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
Oh.
No!
Bad trip!
Oh my god.
Flat stone has appeared.
We can go skipping maybe.
On the lake.
It's bouncing off.
I kind of like that.
Yeah, I don't know how it just took damage.
No clue.
I thought I killed him.
Slice!
Dice!
Spice!
I'm not a big fan of the slice.
It doesn't even do that much damage.
Oh man, really?
No!
That bastard!
We have one HP!
I can't go in demon room.
My ass is on fire.
Oh my god.
Why did I even take a full heart of damage?
Like, this game feels so inconsistent.
I don't understand it.
Usually when you go to the womb, that's when you take a full heart of damage.
Like, why the fuck did I just get killed by one shot?
It doesn't even make sense to me.
I can't get a win, guys.
I think it's over for me.
Game is too hard.
Who do I want?
What about...
Normal set?
No.
Question marks.
Sometimes, you gotta go for the thing you least want to go for, and then it somehow goes right.
You know?
This is one of those times.
It's like the saying of, uh, the best party happens in the places you least expect them to, right?
So if you want the best party in the world, all you gotta do is stay at home, and put on the most boring movie ever.
And then, then a real party happens, you know?
Basically, you gotta set yourself up for failure.
Oh my god.
Maybe not like that.
Not that much failure.
Like, don't go into a corner like that.
Bad idea.
But you get the gist.
Uh, there's a secret in there.
And I can actually do it.
If I blow up here, it's gonna blow up that bomb in there.
Okay, why didn't that bomb in there blow this up, though?
I thought for sure it was in range.
I guess I was wrong.
I thought of being all clever.
Wait, is this gonna set me up nicely for the boss here?
This boss is gonna get smacked.
With this amount of blue flies.
Hey, man.
Oh, that didn't even do that much damage.
I thought he was gonna get one shot.
I had so many flies.
That was actually beautiful.
Stabler.
Uh, we got the treasure room.
We got the...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I think we just move on.
The plan is to go home.
On this character.
Because we haven't managed to do that.
Wait, am I one-shotting them?
Hold on.
How do I have so much damage?
Is it just that one?
I guess it is.
Not bad.
Wait, this room looks exactly like the other room we had.
Just without the secret stone.
Of Hogwarts, or whatever.
Oh, that's the philosopher's stone.
I was like, wait a minute.
Harry Potter and the secret stone?
Doesn't sound right, does it?
Yeah, listen!
It's a great item.
We're already bzzz-ing in here, so that's a great start.
Very underwhelming.
Another bzzz-ing in
here.
Oh, money!
Huge.
Wait, another bzzz-ing in here?
That's three in a row.
The best bomb of all time!
Are you seeing this, guys?
Don't fall into the hole.
Oh.
Oh, man!
I need more blue hearts!
Oh, oof.
Oh, wait.
Hold on.
Double s-
The battery...
I'm drawn to the champion belt.
But I can also- I can grab this- Nah, I'm gonna re-roll.
Fuck it.
If I'm not 100% sold on something, I don't think I should go for it, you know?
Ayy!
I like that one!
The Bible is also solid.
I'm taking this.
Huh?
Oh, right.
Okay.
What's this?
Okay, you know what?
Fuck it.
I'm- I'm becoming small.
I'm not gonna be able to see my character, but it's okay.
Family...
Soul?
Desplace the location of the boss room on the map.
After defeating the floor's boss, automatically activate the Sun Tarot card.
Uh, no.
Botfly.
Orbital familiar that deals contact damage.
I want something that gives me some HP.
No, I'm gonna re-roll again.
Here we go!
Dinner!
Oh, wait, this is just gonna equalize, right?
It's not gonna do anything for me.
Mars!
Friends, a dash attack that can be activated by double-tabbing a move button.
Immune to most damage.
Charge.
The charge.
Also spawns a small ring.
Uh, okay.
Wait, hold on.
I need to understand this.
So Isaac is going to do most damage while charging.
Also spawns a small ring of flames on impact.
Okay.
Uh, it's- it's too- it's too skill-based.
I'm not- I'm- I don't have skill.
Hahaha.
Dark bomb?
No thanks.
Stem cells.
That one is a...
just solid plus 0.16 shot speed.
Because my health is gonna be equalized.
Look!
Haha, not bad.
Uh, duplicates all pickups and item pedestals.
Ooh, wait!
I should've-
Oh, wait a minute, actually.
All item pedestals?
Which means all of these.
I could've had twice the attack speed here.
Whoops.
I'm taking this.
And then I'm gonna- Wait, what?
Hold on.
Why is there no battery indicator on that?
The black bean.
I'm not taking damage.
Isaac releases several farts.
Whoa!
We gotta take that!
We don't know what it is.
I'm gonna- I'm gonna use this now.
It's for free!
Oh my god!
Oh!
Wait, even smaller size.
More tears?
Wait, this is so exciting.
Cube baby!
It's all free!
But I- Guys, I have half a heart!
I have half a heart.
Uh...
Yeah, give me that.
What's this?
Uh...
Okay, sure.
The poop?
Spawn?
Okay.
Oh, that's the one I had.
Ventricle ray- Oh, man.
Guys, I think I went too far on this.
I have no HP.
I can't even see my character.
I'm not gonna be able to dodge shit.
Kinda wanna re-roll again.
Is that crazy?
I mean...
Here's my question.
Let's say I re-roll.
I get an item that says, uh...
Sacrifice one heart, but gain three black hearts.
I wonder if that...
makes me die.
Because I technically lose the heart before I get the three black hearts.
You know what I mean?
It's an experiment.
Oh, okay.
Let's not accidentally pick anything up here.
So what do we get?
Acid baby.
No.
Okay, this one...
Guys, this may be the end of the run.
I'm going to do it.
Wait, is this the one that...
Oh, I want that real bad, actually, but I can't.
I'm gonna take this.
Let's see if I die.
If I die, it's worth the knowledge.
Okay, I don't...
Hey, there we go.
I can't reroll anymore, though.
Okay, I think we're done here.
Hey, we have one heart.
That's something.
Wait, I can't even see my character.
I'm scared, man.
I'm so scared.
Let's get in here.
Glass eye?
I feel like I should, uh...
Buy this pill.
Uh, let's...
I think I'm just gonna do the boss.
Like, uh...
I'm probably gonna die here.
To be honest.
Let me think.
Oh, no, not these!
I'm gonna die!
I'm so...
I'm so terrible against this.
Jesus.
Oh!
Wait, how's the other guy dead?
Huh?
How did the other guy die?
I'm confused.
Well, we can't take any deal...
Wait, we can look...
We can take a look.
No, we can't take it.
Can't take it.
We can't take it.
If it had given us HP, we could have done it.
But we can't.
We gotta move on.
Very exciting, though.
This run is kinda nuts already.
And it's on the third floor.
Oh, no, we're lost!
I can't...
I...
Come on.
Petrified poop.
Hey!
That's really good for me.
Unironically, one of the better items.
I heard the...
Sound again.
I'm starting to think it's maybe a...
Like an easter egg.
That sound, you know.
No, are they the jumping ones?
Jumping jacks?
They're not.
Oh, I couldn't see my character for a second.
I really have to...
I am keeping my eyes trained on my character so I don't lose sight of it.
Oh, no.
They keep shooting.
But...
What?!
Guys, we got it.
Ladies and gentlemen, we've got it.
But at what price...
What price did we pay for this?
We have one HP.
Um...
I'm actually gonna...
Re...
Roll...
I'm not gonna re-roll yet.
We gotta get in here.
Pestilence?
Oh, don't.
Please.
I hope he doesn't have, like, a laser.
Come on.
Oh,
give me HP!
Fuck this cube of meat!
Worst item in the entire game.
Oh, man.
I literally can't see my character.
Okay, let's...
Let's...
We're moving on.
This...
We have half a heart.
This is...
This is bad.
I think we are dead.
Oh, God.
I have to remember, I can pre-charge Brimstone.
Never forgetty.
In Cincinnati.
Be my character, man!
That's too much for me.
That's...
I...
This game is too hard.
I can't win.
Wow.
I'm gonna eat a cookie.
And drink my coffee.
That last run was so much fun, though.
The potential.
The sheer potential of that.
All the stuff that was happening.
I had so many items.
We got Brimstone.
Half a heart was heartbreaking.
Imagine, guys.
If we had had one more blue...
I was too greedy.
That's the problem.
Yeah, chaos was...
The one thing that made this run insane.
You know?
Being able to get any type of item in any room...
Is wild.
The best part is, guys.
My room is the same temperature it was...
When I started.
It hasn't overheated...
Because of my graphics card...
And my CPU.
It's...
It's wild.
What a great feeling.
If anyone is on the fence about an AC...
And you don't have one...
You gotta jump in.
You gotta do it.
No, I didn't get C-section.
I got a C-section.
Booyah!
Your fingers were frozen...
So you couldn't play as well.
You know what?
That's it.
Thank you, chess man.
How many hours do I have spent?
Let me check Steam.
175 hours.
But I've had some breaks in between.
I mean, at this point, Frank...
I'm just trying to play characters...
And get more achievements on them.
You know, like...
For example, trying to go home with...
With, uh...
With the blue boy.
Or trying to...
Kill...
Uh...
Satan on a character...
I haven't killed Satan on and stuff...
Just to get unlocks, right?
That's where I'm at with the progress right now.
The game is on a huge sale.
Oh, actually!
That's right!
There's Steam sale is going on.
I haven't even looked at that yet.
I should really just buy things in bulk right now for the future.
Is there, like, a really good deal?
Other than, uh...
The Binding of Isaac.
Did you guys buy something yet from the Steam sale?
You forgot an Eternal Heart at some point today...
Oh, did I?
Was it during the...
The blue boy run just now?
Or was it earlier?
I don't even remember that I forgot one.
Earlier?
Okay, do you think me picking that up would have saved that run I was on?
I got Dishonored.
Oh, actually!
Dishonored!
I want to play those games, too.
Maybe I should buy that.
There's also a Dishonored, too, right?
And some DLCs.
Hold on, let me actually write it down right now.
I'm gonna write down...
Dishonored Steam sale.
I love...
Getting those games that are, like, 90% discounted in the Steam sales.
Oh, Bioshock...
Is also a game I want to play.
There's, like, three Bioshocks, right?
There's, like, Bioshock...
No, wait, four!
Bioshock 1, 2, 3, and then Bioshock Infinite.
Maybe you can get a pack.
With all games.
When did I start streaming?
Just in general.
On my birthday three years ago.
Unless you mean streaming specifically where I'm live, and not just recording videos over YouTube, then it's a little later.
But, honestly, just check when Minecraft Season 1, Episode 1 is.
Because that's the time I started streaming.
Approximately.
So, 2023...
What's the reason why I started streaming?
Because I've always enjoyed streaming.
Like, I've tried to do it in the past.
You know, I was playing on World of Warcraft private servers for a while.
And...
People in that guild I was in were streaming a lot.
You know, it was fun to watch what they were doing at all times.
I mean, we were just streaming to each other, right?
Like, friends.
And then I would do that as well.
And they would watch my stream.
And we would watch each other's streams like that.
And that's just what we did.
And I always thought it was fun to...
Share that experience of playing a game with someone, you know?
Even though my type of streaming right now is a little different than usual.
Like, I don't really interact with chat during most of the games I play.
I'm playing Sims 1 right now, where I am interacting with chat.
So, that's the only one where I really do that.
But I kind of want to do more, where I interact with chat.
But yeah.
Were you nervous?
I could never.
I would feel so self-conscious.
I mean, I guess so.
A little bit.
Nowadays, no.
But I'm still nervous about, for example, the idea of getting a webcam, you know?
And recording my face while I'm streaming.
I would probably get used to it if I did, but...
I don't know.
I kind of like being able to sit here and...
You know, having my hair messed up and not necessarily showering before I start streaming, you know?
And not looking like a slob.
I mean, maybe I am looking like one, but you can't see it.
There's something appealing about that.
But yeah, I have promised...
If we get to a million subs on YouTube, then I will permanently have a webcam.
I have heard of Sobitwomble.
Isn't that the guy who did a lot of armor videos?
Because I used to be into that.
I used to do some...
A little bit of milsim in some guild, or I don't think it's called a guild.
Maybe a clan?
I used to watch some of his Arma videos.
This was back when DayZ mod for Arma was big.
That's how I got introduced to Arma, actually.
And I played a bit of that.
Yeah, he's fun.
I didn't know that he had the same type of ethics and feelings about streaming.
So how does he do it?
Does he not interact with chat at all, or...?
I'm kind of curious about that.
Or is it just like a minimal type of interaction?
Let me switch this over as well.
Combat music.
Just saw Bioshock collect...
It's $12.
Okay, well then I gotta get it.
Is there like a remastered or something?
Just gonna write it down.
Oh, I already did write it down.
Wow.
Already forgot.
What song is this?
It's from a mod for Battlefield 1942.
Called Desert Combat.
It's amazing.
This song specifically is called Smoke Them Out.
So imagine a bunch of soldiers, you know, clearing houses.
Throwing in smoke grenades.
I don't know when we're gonna do a scary stream.
I feel like I need a big pause between scary games.
The last game I played was...
The Bunker.
Amnesia The Bunker.
And that...
I actually have mental scars from that.
I don't think I'm ready for another scary game yet.
But yeah.
Maybe the next one we do on stream.
And not a recorded series.
No, for Season 3 we're gonna start over, Mr. Tanooki.
It's going to be...
A brand new world.
With mods.
And...
Multiplayer.
I've got four other people lined up.
We're gonna do something.
We have a whole speedrunning section planned as well.
I'm kidding.
No, I'm gonna do mods and a new world.
That's it.
Yeah.
It's gonna be good to play some Minecraft again.
I've been getting the itch, you know?
Silent Hill 1 remake.
Yeah, man.
Silent Hill 2 remake was...
At this point, one of the best games I've ever played.
So I'm definitely looking forward to that.
It's confirmed, right?
Red Dead 2 will happen at some point in Maddie Boom.
Because Red Dead 1 was a masterpiece in my opinion.
And I have to play the second one.
It's just that I don't want to compromise my experience with it.
And right now, I'm having technical issues with it on PC.
So I'm either gonna wait until they fix it on consoles with a next-gen patch.
Or until I get some different hardware in my computer that allows me to play the game without issues.
Do you still remember how to do the Invisibility Potion?
Vaguely.
I don't think I remember the exact steps.
But I think I remember the general idea behind the item that I need for it.
I think I could do it.
Subnautica?
I already played Maddie Boom.
It's on YouTube.
And yes, it was a great game.
Yeah, check it out.
I'm looking forward to Subnautica 2 when it's finished.
I hope...
If they do an Elden Ring 2, I hope they make it less open world.
That was one of the...
In my opinion, at least, less amazing things about the game.
And that's probably a hot take.
I think the...
The quality of the game was...
Kind of watered down by the open world.
Like, it was a nice cake to eat, but it was big.
It was a big cake.
And it was not like every time you took a bite, you were blown away.
It was like, this is pretty good, you know?
Whereas Dark Souls...
Every time you take a bite, it's like the best taste in the world.
And you don't get too full either.
You don't feel bloated after eating it.
God of War?
You think that would be a game for me?
Because I gotta be honest.
I watched a review of it.
I'm talking about the new God of War that came out.
Was it in 2018 or something?
You know how God of War was like a series?
And then they rebooted it with a new game?
And I saw a review of that and people in the review said that there was a lot of hand-holding and NPCs would sort of just tell you the solution to a puzzle.
And that to me immediately felt like, oh, that doesn't sound good.
So I don't know if this is for me then.
That sounds like that would piss me off.
But if the rest of the game is like so good, maybe I'll...
be able to overcome that.
Yeah, the world and story is great?
Okay.
If it is actually so good that it could, you know, outweigh the gameplay...
then I would probably enjoy it.
Gameplay is such a big...
factor in games.
No surprise there, but...
I'm playing XCOM right now and...
XCOM gameplay, like the gameplay design of that game might be...
one of the best gameplay experiences I've had in my life in gaming.
I am freaking addicted to the gameplay loop of XCOM.
You know?
It is so incredibly satisfying to play.
Even if that game didn't have a new story and it does have a story, but it's not like, at least until this point, very big and meaningful.
But even if it didn't have any story, I would still be down, you know?
I just love this sort of...
gameplay, yeah.
I will play Bioshock, hey, John?
I feel like XCOM 2 is much harder for no reason.
Wait, really?
XCOM 1 is already fucking hard.
Damn.
They should make an XCOM 3.
Why is the IP dead?
What is that?
That's bullshit.
Wasn't it pretty popular back in the day?
Quizox?
I don't know, man.
GTA 6?
Here's the thing.
Obviously, it's gonna be a generational game when it comes out and everyone's gonna be talking about it.
Even the normies, you know, will have heard about this game.
And will be talking about this game.
And I could, you know, buy it as soon as it comes out and play it on PlayStation or Xbox or whatever.
But I'm pretty sure it's gonna be in 30 frames per second.
Yes, it's gonna be hype to play it with everyone else, but they're gonna release a PC version, you know, with unlocked FPS at some point.
And I just can't stop thinking, why would I not wait for that?
It's gonna be such a better experience.
But who knows?
I haven't decided yet.
Maybe the hype is gonna be so big that I can't resist.
I'll have to wait and see.
PC specs, I have 7800X3D, 64 gigs of RAM.
I forget the exact type of RAM.
6000 something.
And RTX 5090.
Which is one of the reasons why I'm so sad I can't even fucking play Red Dead 2, you know?
But it's probably nothing to do with the strength of my equipment.
It's just a random situation where the combination of my PC components results in the game not working for me.
Oh yeah, I heard the drama about the game.
It's like 80 bucks, right?
And 100 bucks for some basic content or something?
I don't know the specifics, but that sounds horrible.
What specs am I wearing glasses?
See-through...
Cheap-ass glasses from Specsavers.
In Denmark, it's called Louis Nielsen.
Yeah, I'm down for Horizon Zero Dawn at some point.
I heard it's really optimized, which is always very appealing to me.
If a game has its technical debt taken care of, and it runs well, it's nicely optimized, a few bucks, that is already so important for me.
That in itself could make a game 6 out of 10, you know, without anything else.
It just means that much to me.
I don't know if I'm near or short-sighted.
I don't know what the right word is.
I can't see things far away, but I can see things close up.
What is that called?
I guess I would be short-sighted, right?
Because I see things...
Yeah, near-sighted.
Short-sighted is a different thing.
G-game, let's just hear it.
What kind of suggestions do you have?
I'll pull up the backlog now and add them.
I mean, the backlog is already so big, you know, but...
I will add it.
What did you write?
Supraland.
I think that may already be in my backlog.
Or maybe...
Yeah, it's already there.
It's already in my backlog.
The Messenger, Iconoclasts, and Faith, the Unho...
I've never even heard of those games.
But I'm gonna put him on the log.
2018, I guess.
Iconoclasts sounds cool.
That's a cool name.
Wait, it's not even released?
Is it an early access or something?
Or Iconoclasts?
Oh, okay, with an S at the end, I see.
There's a difference.
And then you said Faith, the Unholy...
Okay, that's not showing up.
There we go.
May have been added, sir.
By the way, by the way, if you want to see the backlog, this is the backlog.
It's pretty cool.
Actually, you should, uh, yeah, you should click on backlog first.
I forgot to add the full link.
I've not played Fallout New Vegas.
My sister wants me to play it real bad.
Because she's, like, a huge Fallout fan.
And she keeps bugging me about it.
I should listen to my sister.
You're right.
I introduced her to World of Warcraft, and now she's addicted, so I'm, like, the worst brother ever.
I basically gave her crack.
I shouldn't have done that.
That was a mistake.
I don't know if she's tried Minecraft.
I think she must have.
Because she knows what Minecraft is, and, uh, all the creatures in it.
Okay, guys, I'm out of here.
I had a blast today, even though I kept losing.
I am just so happy that I can finally play my games without sweating to death in this climate.
We're gonna have more streams now.
Like, it's gonna be so much more comfortable.
Yeah.
And next, uh, month, of course, we start Minecraft season 3.
That's gonna be wild.
Haha!
Alright.
I'll see you around.
Peace out.
And this is the second one.